Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 45, folder: 20 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: Annual Report 1955, Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Understanding The New York Stock Exchange, Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Statement of G. Keith Funston Before the Committee on Banking and Currency United States Senate, Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Box: 45, folder: 21 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Cure-all or Booby-Trap, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: New York Telephone, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Organization Charts, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: New York Telepohone, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Bell System Interconnection Policy Being Considered in FCC Hearings, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Organization Charts, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: here's the Job we have to do, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: One Million Owners, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: Long Range Business Policies A Case Study, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
    By Keith S. McHugh. January 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: New York TelephoneYour Business A Reference Guide for Management, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Box: 45, folder: 22 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between The Upstate Telephone Employees' Association And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Agreement Between Telephone Traffic Union (N.Y.) And New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Agreement Between Telephone Traffic Union Upstate New York and New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Agreement Between The Union of Telephone Workers And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: The Union of Telephone Workers And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: Wage Reopening Agreement Between The Union Of Telephone Workers And New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 7: Agreement Between Telephone Traffic Union (New York) And New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 8: Constitution And By-Laws Telephone Traffic Union Upstate New York, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 9: Agreement Between The Union Of Telephone Workers And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 10: Wage Reopening Agreement Between the Telephone Traffic Union Upstate New York and the New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 11: Agreement between the Telephone Commercial Union and the New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 12: Agreement Between The Union Of Telephone Workers And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 13: Agreement between the Telephone Commercial Union and the New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 14: Agreement Between The Union Of Telephone Workers And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 15: Agreement Between The New York Telephone Company And Telephone Employees' Organization Accounting Department, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 16: Agreement Between Telephone Traffic Union Upstate New York and New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
    December 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Agreement Between The Upstate Telephone Employees' Association And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 18: Agreement Between The Upstate Telephone Employees' Association And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 19: Agreement Between The Upstate Telephone Employees' Association And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 20: Agreement Between Telephone Traffic Union Upstate New York and New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 21: By-Laws Central Office Council Telephone Employees' Organization, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 22: Constitution of the Upstate Telephone Employees' Association, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 23: Agreement between the Telephone Commercial Employees' Association New York Upstate Area and the New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 24: Agreement Between The Upstate Telephone Employees' Association And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
    December 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Agreement Between Traffic Employees' Association Upstate Area and New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 26: Agreement Between Telephone Traffic Union Upstate New York and New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 27: Your Blood Bank, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 28: Agreement Between Telephone Traffic Union Upstate New York and New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 29: Agreement between the Telephone Commercial Union and the New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 30: Constitution And By-Laws of the Traffic Employees' Association Upstate Area New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 31: Agreement Between Telephone Traffic Union Upstate New York and New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 32: Agreement between the Telephone Commercial Union and the New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
    October 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Wage Reopening Agreement Between The Upstate Telephone Employees' Association And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 34: Agreement between the Telephone Commercial Employees' Association, New York Upstate Area and the New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 35: Agreement Between Telephone Employees' Organization Accounting Department And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 36: Wage Opening Agreement Between Telephone Traffic Union (New York) And New York Telephone Company Containing Revised Wage Schedules, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 37: Agreement between the Telephone Commercial Employees' Association, New York Upstate Area and the New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 38: Agreement Between The Upstate Telephone Employees' Association And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 39: Agreement between the Empire State Telephone Workers' Organization and the New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
    Januaryy 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Modification Of Agreement Between Telephone Traffic Union Upstate New York and New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 41: Agreement Between Traffic Employees' Association Manhattan, Long Island, And Bronx-Westchester Areas And New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
    October 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Agreement Between Telephone Traffic Union Upstate New York and New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 43: Agreement Between The New York Telephone Company And Telephone Employees' Organization Accounting Department, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 44: Agreement Between The Upstate Telephone Employees' Association And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 45: Agreement between Telephone Traffic Union (New York) and New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 46: To Upstate Area Telephone People:, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 47: Wiring Council, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 48: Present Employee Delegates, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 49: Telephone Employees' Organization - Manhattan Plant Department New York Telephone Company - Construction And Engineering Force, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 50: This We Believe, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
    May/June. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Stipulation Between The New York Telephone Company And The Telephone Traffic Union, Upstate New York, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 52: Agreement Between The Upstate Telephone Employees' Association And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 53: Agreement Between The New York Telephone Company And Telephone Employees' Organization Accounting Department, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 54: Wage Reopening Agreement Between The Telephone Employees' Organization, Accounting Department And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 55: Wage Reopening Agreement Between The Telephone Employees' Organization, Accounting Department And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 56: To All Management Employees, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 57: Wage Reopening Agreement Between The Union Of Telephone Workers And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 58: Wage Reopening Agreement Between The Union Of Telephone Workers And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 59: Wage Reopening Agreement Between Th eTelephone Traffic Union (New York) And The New York Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 60: Attachment B, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Box: 45, folder: 23 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: mbw news, Publication (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Box: 45, folder: 24 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Tamiment Library, Publication (Box 45, Folder 24)
    By Daniel Bell. Item is in English.